Why you are so obsessed about Sham
Brian? For some reason she felt like she
needed to lie about credentials. A world
where we act like credentials is what
determines somebody's effectiveness.
>> If I'm about to get a surgery and the
mother surgeon DON'T HAVE CREDENTIALS,
DON'T come near me.
>> It's not the same thing.
>> Psychology is open heart surgery on your
brain and what you think. It's the same
thing.
>> What are you talking about?
>> Now you guys might not remember Amanda.
>> Low key noble.
>> And even if it was a hoax for the sake
of bringing attention to this, then I'm
like that's low key noble. Like I'm just
>> We had made a video about her behavior
and I just want y'all to just see a bit
of it.
>> So I heard that there's some young men
who have made a video about me being a
narcissist.
Um
>> Guess who that is.
>> [ __ ] you guessed it.
>> You
>> You was right. You was right.
>> Apparently [laughter] we're old school
classic.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yo, LOOK AT YOUR SHIRT. I'M SORRY.
>> THAT SHIRT.
>> Instead of using that time to make a
video that can actually be helpful.
Making a video that is, you know,
educating folks on Remy Reid who
>> Yeah, that was true. I forgot about
that. She was like, why don't you talk
about this guy who was
And then we had just talked about two
other people who were on the
>> You talk about a Boat Man John?
>> We we did a bunch of videos about him,
too. I did at least three.
>> That's why her criticism was not
memorable.
>> mouth Make a video about that.
>> Make a video about that. Why don't you
give it up? Why can't we do both?
>> faced
>> That's facts. Why can't you do both?
>> This would be an easy interview.
>> I'm ready to address whatever.
>> First of all, are you still on Insecure?
>> What kind of dumb ass QUESTION IS THAT?
>> [laughter]
[screaming]
>> LET'S GO BACK IN THE PAST
>> [laughter]
>> BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT? IF YOU want to
predict the future, sometimes you just
got to look at history.
>> It is crazy for us
>> [laughter]
>> to react to an old clip of us to us
reacting to an old clip of us.
>> Seven years later in the exact same way.
>> always makes me laugh.
>> I'M HERE I'M HERE TO ADDRESS EVERYTHING.
What kind of DUMB ASS WAS
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S NEVER NOT FUNNY.
>> WHAT KIND OF DUMB ASS WAS I?
>> I'M just Next question.
>> Well, who was the person that did not
like you?
>> No, we're not doing that. But
>> What are YOU TALKING TO?
>> [laughter]
>> HEY, I'M NOT GOING TO LIE. THAT THAT WAS
A MOMENT. THAT WAS [laughter] A MOMENT.
THAT WAS A MOMENT.
I guess what it feels like.
>> We were wearing the same colors.
I [snorts] was wearing black. She was
wearing black. And she
>> Yeah, but this is all on purpose. Why
you pretend like it's not?
>> [laughter]
>> Don't lie. Don't act like you didn't
pre-watch.
>> What? How?
>> [laughter]
>> You pre-watched. Don't Don't act like
you didn't pre-pre. Don't do that. Let's
not be fake for the audience. Oh,
authentic moment. We just happened to do
that by accident. Don't do that. Don't
do that.
>> you doing this?
>> Don't act like I didn't send you a text
message.
>> the text.
>> You want me to huh?
>> Show me the text.
Where's your degree?
>> Huh?
>> Where's your degree?
>> Would you like to see MY COSTCO CARD?
>> [laughter]
>> WHAT ARE WE DOING?
>> IT'S GOOD.
>> [laughter]
>> THE FACT THAT WE'RE WEARING THE SAME
[ __ ] is kind of trippy.
>> I think some people don't like me
because I may reflect something that
they desire.
>> That's the reason why some people might
not like you.
But why does NOBODY LIKE YOU?
>> [laughter]
[screaming]
>> OH, NO, BRO.
>> I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
THAT WAS TIMING. THAT was mint.
>> But that's the face that I'll be talking
about where you said, "No, you on some
bullshit." THAT'S MY FACE [laughter]
RIGHT THERE.
>> THE context of this is that she goes on
a bunch of podcasts to talk about the
fact that she was blacklisted from a
party. So, it starts this big thing with
Issa Rae, who at the time was a mega
star in regards to Hollywood and
television. You know, she goes on to
call everyone in the industry who hates
her, which is hundreds of people who
have worked with her. A lot of them
evil, mean-spirited. And so the
interview was actually kind of funny
because turns out everyone had valid
reasons to hate her. Sure enough, when
all of this started happening, I was
super curious to hear what she was going
to say about this whole situation.
>> Why are you also obsessed about Cheyenne
Bryant? I'm beginning to think that this
is a bot thing.
>> A bot thing?
>> Why are you so obsessed about this?
Like, okay, she lied.
I could see if she lied and like harmed
people,
but she was on my podcast and she was
brilliant.
>> [snorts]
>> So,
it's not about a podcast appearance.
This is about treating people.
Oh, she messed up a bunch of people and
she's not really she's taking advantage
of the community.
You're the one that's quick to [ __ ]
say that people are taking advantage of
the the community. You were talking
about patriarchy. You were talking about
this. You got someone taking advantage
of the community by faking that they're
a professional.
But you know, you're a girly girl.
You're a girly pop. You're girls' girls,
right? She just lied. You're talking
about the patriarchy. If it was a man
taking advantage of women, you'd be
like, "OH MY GOD, PATRIARCHY."
>> And I do want to say there are people
that she did do sessions with that were
harmed by her that did come out. And I
did mention one of them who spoke out
very publicly.
She was a person who was shot in the
head. I think she was in Iraq when she
got shot. And so she does have head
trauma and PTSD. And she decided to do a
session with her and that session
actually sent her spiraling into a bad
place. So the idea that she hasn't
harmed people, that's just one instance,
but you also think of the other
instances where she's pretending to
represent a field. She's pretending to
have a knowledge base and speaking from
authority as well as like research and
academic background, but she's not. And
she's using her own bro science and
spreading it out there while using that
[ __ ] profession as a shield. So she's
misrepresenting the work that a lot of
mental health advocates do. And beyond
that, too,
as someone who talks about the fact
that, you know, black folks are
mistrusting of the whole health industry
for valid reasons,
having a fraudulent psychologist be the
face of psychology in the black
community sounds like a pretty horrible
thing.
>> Yo, [ __ ] that Abba. She was going on my
podcast.
>> What are you even on?
>> That's it.
>> What are you So, be [ __ ] all of that.
>> Yep.
>> All of what Abba was saying
content.
>> That's your argument.
>> No, her argument is one that you know
very well, which is low-key noble.
>> Low-key noble.
>> That's low-key noble.
>> She's low-key noble.
>> Remember when she said Jussie Smollett
is low-key noble.
>> Even though she admitted that he faked
that whole hate crime. She's like,
"Well, he was bringing attention to a
real thing." This girl truly is the
worst for me.
>> I think it's [ __ ] up that she lied.
You know, and then that's that. The the
the need to
If y'all went this hard against like
Kamala Harris for supporting a genocide,
then like
what would
That That would matter to me.
Why are you all so obsessed about
Shayenne Bryant? I don't I don't have
There's no match. I don't need to have
some type of debate with Dr. Shayenne
Bryant with Shayenne Bryant. At the end
of the day, for some reason, she felt
like she needed to lie about
credentials.
>> They follow what?
>> I don't know why.
I think part of the reason is because we
live in a a world where we act like
credentials is what determines
somebody's effectiveness across the
board. And then
>> Pause. YOU DON'T WHAT? SOMETIMES, YEAH.
IF I'M ABOUT TO GET A SURGERY and the
[ __ ] surgeon don't have
credentials, don't come near me.
What are you talking about?
IF I'M ABOUT TO HAVE OPEN HEART surgery
and guess what? Guess what? It's not the
same thing. Psychology is open heart
surgery on your brain and what you
think. And the whole way of thinking.
It's the same thing.
>> Pause. Pause. Pause. Pause. Can we just
take a second?
>> Value.
Value.
>> Yes, sir.
Yeah.
It is.
>> REPEAT THAT [ __ ] NOT BECAUSE YOU DON'T
HAVE YOUR OPEN HEART, BUT IT'S YOUR open
mind. What are you talking about? WHAT
ARE YOU TALKING YOU COULD SERIOUSLY [ __ ]
UP SOMEONE if they think that you have
the credential BECAUSE THEY WILL LAY
THEY WILL LEAVE their hope and trust in
you.
>> Yeah.
>> And then just like a Geppetto, you're
going to do whatever you want with the
perpetuity of your so-called master that
you do NOT HAVE WITH THAT PERSON. IT IS
EXACTLY LIKE OPEN HEART SURGERY.
THE [ __ ] IS WRONG with you?
>> I also think it's odd for artists to say
that. Like you're essentially endorsing
the idea that she steals other people's
credits.
>> It's got to You know what I mean?
>> You know what I'm saying? Like so I I
don't know. To me, it's just something
very odd about this whole dynamic where
she's like, "Oh well, people act like
credentials mean something." Yeah, they
do.
We have no way of checking everyone's
background every single day to make sure
that they have years of experience or
whatever it is. So we rely on these
credentials and the fact that you're
state licensed to say that you've met
the minimum requirements to be able to
hold and do this profession and you meet
these standards.
Yeah. Like I I don't even know where
this is coming from or why she would say
this stuff. Well, let's keep listening.
>> In some [clears throat] respects, it is
absolutely necessary. And in her
respect, it actually wasn't necessary
for her to do the work that she does.
That being said, I just don't care.
I don't care. She was on my podcast and
she was incredible. I don't care.
I think it sucks and I think it was not
smart and I think that at the end of the
day, there are people who work really
hard to get doctorates. There are also
people who call themselves doctor when
they get an honorary doctorate and I
don't think that's much different.
>> Woah, nobody cares that Woah, woah.
>> Dr. Dre does beats. He doesn't [ __ ]
tell people what to do with their lives.
>> canceling [ __ ] Dr. Pepper because
he's not offering treatment. Okay,
nobody's mad at Dr. Seuss because he not
pretend to be a psychologist and then
Oh my days.
>> Do it to his defense, that cat was in
the hat.
Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know what I'm doing.
I don't know what kind of day it
>> Guys, this is so mundane. Like she
doesn't address random petty [ __ ] all
the time. In fact, when she got big
popular off that Breakfast Club
interview, it's because of her little
drama with some of the people she works
with. Like we nobody looked at her then
and be like, "Why don't you talk about
this? Why don't you talk about that?" We
just let you yap on about how you were
mistreated by people. It's so funny to
watch people and their excuses for why
you shouldn't discuss a topic are always
just like shaming as if they don't talk
about the more mundane or more I don't
even think it's mundane or
insignificant. When the biggest person
within a community as a mental health
practitioner is a total fraud, that is a
big deal, especially when that community
has issues with the health industry. It
is a big deal. It's fine if you want to
address other stuff, but why I don't
know, man. I hate that so much. Why
don't you talk about Ukraine? Why don't
you talk about this? It's like, "Okay,
can we ever talk about nothing related
to world matters? Is that not possible?
Do we always have to talk about these
things? And you realize this is just a
thing where they want to position
themselves as the person who's doing the
moral righteous thing, so you should
never discuss this topic. And it's
[ __ ]
>> Actually, Dr. Pepper was actually
invented in 1885 by a young pharmacist
named Charles Alderton. It is a widely
believed to be named after Dr. Charles
T. Pepper, a physician and sir he is a
doctor. So even Dr. Pepper has more
credentials than Shaun Bryant. Anyways,
>> Maya Angelou was walking around calling
herself Dr. Maya Angelou. She didn't
complete a doctorate. Some university
gave her a doctorate.
>> Damn, she even threw Maya Angelou under
the bus. To my knowledge, Maya Angelou
was incredibly accomplished in terms of
literary work in her fields, that she
has created a lot of works within that
field, and but she hasn't gone on to do
treatment.
>> She doesn't go outside be treating
people and be like, "I'm wrong." She's a
writer.
>> You're right. You're right.
>> She's heavily rewarded.
>> She's not just heavily rewarded to my
knowledge. Is she Does she do
treatments?
>> No. She's a writer.
>> Maya Angelou was not a medical doctor
and did not offer medical treatment.
However, as a prominent advocate for
women's health, she supported medical
issues and lent her name to different
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> So, you going to throw Maya Angelou
under the bus as if she's Cheyenne
Bryant when all she did was support
health No one would have an issue with
Cheyenne Bryant if she did that. No one
would have an issue with Cheyenne Bryant
if she called herself just doctor based
off her doctorate. The issue with
Cheyenne Bryant is she pretended to be a
licensed therapist, which she never was.
And that she pretended to have a degree
that she never received, that she did an
academic paper that it never happened,
and that she was offering people medical
treatment. Like these comparisons that
she's making it I don't know. But that
that that's my read on Amanda Seales. I
actually think I think activism has so
many [ __ ] narcissists it's
unbelievable. The people who attach
themselves to wars and conflicts to be
able to have this idea of like I'm a
righteous person, but it's only a
convenient vehicle for them. It's a
convenient vehicle for them because once
they attach themselves to this idea of
oppression or whatever it is, what they
do is they become a symbol and they get
all this adulation from people who like
review them as a hero. And that's what
they're there for. But they throw that
[ __ ] away, they throw ethics away, they
don't give a [ __ ] about none of these
principles the moment they get a chance.
Because this this conflict is just a a
thing for them to use to be able to
shield themselves from any criticism
whilst also getting respect for people.
Why would you ever advocate for somebody
fraudulently pretending to be a medical
Because she had good content. She was
good on her podcast.
>> Yes.
>> She looks good, she was good on her
podcast, was cool with me, so you know,
and I'm a girls girl, so you know.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, girlies.
>> Someone said, "Yo, maybe Dr. Bryant is
the one who diagnosed Amanda Seales with
autism." You remember that?
>> And so, I recently was diagnosed as
someone who has autism spectrum
disorder.
>> Cuz Amanda Seales was pretending that
she was diagnosed and she yelled at
Shannon Sharpe. And then when Shannon's
like, "Who diagnosed you?" She's like,
"Don't worry about it. Someone did." And
then she came on a social media post
later admitted she was never diagnosed.
>> Yes. No, I have not been clinically
diagnosed by a doctor because I'm not
paying $10,000.
>> I remember that.
>> I don't know. It It is fascinating to
see someone be like, "I'm for women. I'm
for women." And like when another woman
is actually harming everyday women
>> Well, she's for
>> because you have a relationship with
her, you don't give a [ __ ] That's why
all this patriarchy stuff is always so
funny to me cuz these people will throw
their women under the bus if it's their
girlfriend.
>> Yep.
>> That's the one who's accused of her.
>> what is
I don't want to throw you girlies under
the bus, but I've seen that behavior a
lot. And at a smaller scale to a smaller
scale, you know, when you have a group
of girls, all right, and one of your
girlies don't like another girl, right?
What you going to do? Oh, that girl is
just [ __ ] She's [ __ ] ugly, right? No,
you're the most beautiful girl in the If
it's your friend, she's the most
beautiful girl in the world. But if you
hate that [ __ ] that [ __ ] is ugly,
she's stupid,
uh [ __ ] that girl. Even if it's not
true. Doesn't matter. That's my girl,
and my girl is more beautiful than you.
Mhm.
And [clears throat] be Cuz if Amanda
Seals is the girl with her, well, she's
good. She's all right. She's right.
YOU GIRLS, Y'ALL GUILTY OF THAT. I got
to say. I see that. Have you seen her?
And
I'm looking at her, and she looks
perfectly fine.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> And your friend be looking busted.
But it's your friend. Your friend can do
no wrong.
>> Some people in the chat are going uh
Sneako.
>> How's it going?
I'm sorry.